<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
  <channel>
    <title>78% Sports</title>
    <link>https://www.78percentsports.com/rss.xml</link>
    <description>A podcast with 78% sports and 22% nonsense.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <itunes:author>Erik Patmalnieks &amp; Ryan Belous</itunes:author>
    <itunes:email>78percentsports@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    <itunes:category text="Sports"/>
    <itunes:image href="https://www.78percentsports.com/78percentsports-square.png"/>
    <itunes:explicit>yes</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:complete>no</itunes:complete>
    <item>
      <title>College Football and Otosclerosis</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee6a42f6-22aa-4ded-83f8-b2daa35a7212</guid>
      <description>Erik is by himself today talking about college football and his disdain for Jim Harbaugh. Then, he gives the long answer on what happened with his ears causing two surgeries.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_8_29_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="41710661"/>
      <itunes:duration>35:13</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>40 Bold Fantasy Football Predictions</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70e91003-4c95-4e93-ab8b-f99e29a54e54</guid>
      <description>We each came up with 20 of our boldest fantasy football predictions for the 2019 NFL season. Some things we are completely opposite on so it will be very interesting to see how the season plays out. Tune in for last minute advice to help you win your league!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_8_22_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="58319898"/>
      <itunes:duration>50:41</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 NFL Season Predictions</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6df87e7-97ea-438d-8730-9de467d7cb16</guid>
      <description>Taking a break from fantasy this week, we pick division winners, wild cards, conference championships, and Super Bowl winners in this NFL-only podcast. Some bold predictions in this one so be sure to let us know what you think!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_8_15_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="63586844"/>
      <itunes:duration>54:48</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Football Mock Draft</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a656d797-5b6b-4e39-a400-fd96feca9ade</guid>
      <description>Today we did a live, 10 team, PPR mock draft for fantasy football! We explain each draft pick as it's made and talk about draft strategy overall as a whole. Whether it's your first time playing or if you're a seasoned veteran, there are great tips and advice throughout this one!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 8 Aug 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_8_8_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="69803225"/>
      <itunes:duration>59:49</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Football Sleepers &amp; Keepers</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">583f1c57-f6aa-416b-aaa8-bbcce85ca90e</guid>
      <description>We are in full fantasy football mode now! This episode is all about the sleepers and keepers in this year's draft. A sleeper is a guy ranked outside of the top 15 at his position that will massively outperform his average draft position. A keeper is a player under the age of 25 that you'll want to draft in the late rounds that can lead your team to victory for the next decade.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 1 Aug 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_8_1_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="50646310"/>
      <itunes:duration>44:36</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Football Studs &amp; Duds</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e3a6c76-6309-4e0b-a59e-ab0f0bf99917</guid>
      <description>Finally, our first fantasy football podcast! We pick two studs and two duds ranked in the top 15 at each position. A stud will bring you home a championship and a dud will ruin your season! A must listen for anyone desperate for some fantasy football!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_7_25_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="53024257"/>
      <itunes:duration>45:03</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL 2019 Season Wins Over/Under</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8b8ecbf-23f2-42a7-b0fc-b22e99681ffe</guid>
      <description>With the 2019 NFL season quickly approaching, we go through each team in the league and give our prediction for the number of wins the team will have when the season is all said and done.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_7_18_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="61306227"/>
      <itunes:duration>53:06</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Free Agency Aftermath</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9816721-c9e0-4e15-ae17-a790b2ef5db9</guid>
      <description>Now that Kawhi Leonard has signed, it is time to evaluate the outcome of the first few weeks of NBA free agency. Who got better? Who got worse? We talk about the pure chaos that happened around the league, from the Nets to the Clippers to the Knicks and much more.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_7_11_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="49573540"/>
      <itunes:duration>42:58</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Favorite Athletes</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3483cf1d-e402-45fe-819c-98c441da713a</guid>
      <description>Chris Sollars and Gabe McInchak join us to discuss who our favorite athletes were growing up, both nationally and locally in all four major sports. The first fantasy football question of the year gets asked at the end, and Ryan gives a bold answer.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 4 Jul 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_7_4_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="43551502"/>
      <itunes:duration>39:35</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Halfway Point</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0479ec2-a439-4880-ba11-f075a02b37af</guid>
      <description>Back in March, we made predictions for division winners, wild card teams, league winners, Cy Young winners, MVPs and World Series winners for the 2019 MLB season. Now that the season is almost halfway over, we check to see how well those predictions have held up in this baseball only episode.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_6_27_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="53435027"/>
      <itunes:duration>47:29</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA Offseason</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be73f1ca-03f0-4058-aa0f-26d48ec9e021</guid>
      <description>On the heels of a Toronto Raptors championship, we do a deep dive into the exciting, upcoming NBA offseason. The championship, free agency, the Anthony Davis trade, and the NBA draft all get discussed in this basketball heavy podcast. During the final question, Ryan quickly tries to predict where all the major free agents are going to sign this offseason.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_6_20_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="52683259"/>
      <itunes:duration>46:11</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan Q&amp;A</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5753efc-8137-435d-b97d-b769aeac978b</guid>
      <description>We asked our fans what they wanted us to talk about and they delivered. From the dumbest thing we've done drunk to our favorite cereal to the origin of Hoyt Botch, this episode is packed with nonsense.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_6_13_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="54490466"/>
      <itunes:duration>48:35</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playing Catch Up</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2668288c-db4c-4fff-ad27-b9a1783f33c1</guid>
      <description>A lot can happen in two weeks! We talk about Ryan's staycation and Erik's trip to The Bahamas. Then, we catch up with The NBA Finals and share our prediction of who will win. MLB draft results are next, specifically with what the Detroit Tigers did. Lastly, the NFL OTAs have started and that has us excited for football, so we try to figure out the intriguing NFC North.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 6 Jun 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_6_6_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="52487777"/>
      <itunes:duration>45:59</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Series Finale</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a69974a-45f5-4f32-b2ed-9cde3057eadd</guid>
      <description>Ryan liked the Game of Thrones series finale. Erik absolutely hated it. We discuss all of the things that happened in the final episode and the final season as a whole. Erik then offers up some alternate endings that are far superior to the one revealed this past Sunday night. A must listen for any Game of Thrones fan!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_5_23_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="48913956"/>
      <itunes:duration>43:03</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chiarelli's Market</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bea23408-3134-4bfa-89a8-6bb628f33324</guid>
      <description>We both worked our first jobs and met at a small meat market in Lincoln Park named Chiarelli's Market, roughly 20 years ago. This podcast is dedicated to the absolute nonsense that happened there leading to us becoming best friends. If anyone named Chiarelli listens to this, we want to apologize in advance!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_5_16_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="60357228"/>
      <itunes:duration>53:25</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOATs &amp; Busts</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc3385d-39bc-460d-aacf-bbc97d0caa6c</guid>
      <description>This episode is all about the GOATs, the Greatest Of All Time in each sport. We talk about their incredible accomplishments, insane records, and why they are the best ever at their respective sport. Then we talk about the complete opposite end of the spectrum, the worst Busts of all time. They are guys who were highly thought of that failed to live up to expectations and had disastrous careers.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 9 May 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_5_9_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="50515407"/>
      <itunes:duration>44:43</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 NFL Draft Results &amp; The Battle of Winterfell</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9eb1f74-5b10-4d71-a2d9-538a58530df0</guid>
      <description>The NFL Draft has come and gone, so it's time to discuss yet again how badly the Detroit Lions screwed this one up. We talk about the other NFL teams as well, mainly the ones that had the most interesting drafts and admire how real, competent franchises operate. Then we discuss the mind blowing episode of Game of Thrones that contained the long-awaited Battle of Winterfell.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 2 May 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_5_2_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="57859316"/>
      <itunes:duration>51:35</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April Check-In</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb5148bc-41b6-43ea-bdc2-f6974ae3c17d</guid>
      <description>April is possibly the busiest month of the year when it comes to sports, so we check in with each league to see what's going on. For the NBA, we talk about the Detroit Pistons getting swept. The NHL, we talk about Steve Yzerman's return to Detroit. We give our early impressions on the young MLB season. Then, we add a few last minute thoughts on the NFL draft. A great episode for fans of all sports!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_4_25_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="52923051"/>
      <itunes:duration>47:02</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Mock Draft 2019</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5090ac9-59df-47a4-a9ab-81dcbecb9348</guid>
      <description>Each of us did our own mock drafts for next week's NFL Draft. In this week's episode, we compare our results. Who goes number one overall? Who do the Detroit Lions take? What do the Oakland Raiders do with three first round picks? Tune in to find out!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_4_18_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="61963454"/>
      <itunes:duration>52:11</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones &amp; Sports Hodgepodge</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff3a71da-de7d-428c-bc58-d835385ae143</guid>
      <description>With the Game of Thrones final season premiere airing this Sunday, we give our predictions for what will happen and who will end up claiming the iron throne when all is said and done. Sports Hodgepodge comes next with a bunch of random, quick topics occuring recently in the world of sports.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_4_11_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="46077573"/>
      <itunes:duration>42:08</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 Questions</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16e98e86-ea7f-421b-b339-99b912613498</guid>
      <description>We ask each other 20 of the most ridiculous, random, stupid, idiotic questions you could think of with a few sports questions thrown in to break up the total nonsense.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 4 Apr 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_4_4_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="45740024"/>
      <itunes:duration>44:15</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2019 MLB Season Predictions</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d97bd081-930e-40ff-88b1-0e050b29ebeb</guid>
      <description>It's Opening Day 2019! In a baseball heavy episode, we predict the following for the American and National leagues: division winners, wild card teams, league winner, Cy Young winner, and MVP. The World Series winner is saved for last. Baseball is back!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_3_28_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="50019470"/>
      <itunes:duration>47:43</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL Free Agency &amp; March Madness</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b56b295-b434-46a1-a8e6-95477187635c</guid>
      <description>Now that the dust has settled upon this year's NFL free agency, we break down the notable moves throughout the league. Also, get some last minute March Madness bracket advice as we reveal our Final Four teams and NCAA champion for 2019.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_3_21_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="42302837"/>
      <itunes:duration>40:48</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our First Guest</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09578b59-a726-4982-882b-4a911b78b3b4</guid>
      <description>Our first guest, Chris Sollars, joins us as we share some great stories, ranging from something that happened 10 minutes before the show to way back in high school. Get to know us better and gear up for some big laughs. No sports. All nonsense.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_3_14_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="51514753"/>
      <itunes:duration>47:39</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fantasy Baseball Sleepers &amp; Keepers</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b18ffe0-b790-4144-9d8e-996be475dc89</guid>
      <description>Another new segment - "Sleepers &amp; Keepers." We give you two "Sleepers" from each position in baseball ranked outside of the top 10 that will have excellent years and help deliver your fantasy team a championship. A "Keeper" is a guy under the age of 25 that you'll want on your team for years to come. Take notes as we recommend one for each position.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 7 Mar 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_3_7_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="50065671"/>
      <itunes:duration>47:40</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contenders, Pretenders, Studs &amp; Duds</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76d2b10d-8e62-4a01-8847-d91b9e475961</guid>
      <description>Two new segments get introduced to the show - "Contender or Pretender?" and "Studs &amp; Duds." If the NBA playoffs started today, we determine which teams would be real contenders for the championship or phony pretenders. Studs &amp; Duds involves us examining the top 10 fantasy baseball players at each position and determining a "Stud" who will have a great year and a "Dud" who will have a terrible year. And of course, a hilarious final question. Enjoy!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_2_28_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="65878126"/>
      <itunes:duration>01:03:15</itunes:duration>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast #1</title>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66ae20cd-7d16-4846-926a-3c0c9d713ed2</guid>
      <description>Our first podcast! We talk about what to expect on the show now and in the future. Then, we give fantasy baseball draft advice: What to watch out for, tips &amp; tricks, what not to do, and more. Lastly, we discuss the potential MLB rule changes for the upcoming season and beyond.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/78percentsports/podcast_2_21_2019.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="36828052"/>
      <itunes:duration>35:44</itunes:duration>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
